The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Little fellow...
What the...
Did you think resisting Heaven's Might was the end ?
This
is just the beginning !
Soul Seizing !
You wish !
Your Origin Soul
is mine.
For countless years,
I have been devouring every single cultivator
that reached Ascendant in the Demon Spirit Land.
Scram !
This spell is really strange.
If I hadn't used my killing intent to stay conscious,
my Origin Soul would have been extracted by now.
I must leave quickly.
This arm
was able to breach the restrictions of the Celestial's cave.
I can't underestimate it.
Since I just reached Ascendant,
my cultivation is unstable.
I should seek the Ancient Demon Spirit first
to have him help me find another spot to cultivate.
He actually escaped...
A Defiant Cultivator
really is troublesome...
I was gravely wounded
by the battle back then.
I need origin energy to recover my cultivation.
But origin energy
only manifests when an outsider reaches Ascendant.
Having a fresh Ascendant cultivator is really rare...
How could I let you go !?
He interfered with the teleportation formation...
Who the hell is this person ?
Celestial Ascension Fruits Field\NFire Demon Country
These are...
Celestial Ascension Fruits ?
It's said that consuming them can briefly increase cultivation
but they can also awaken killing intent or the true desires of the heart.
They can cause a severe intoxicating feeling
that could lead to succumbing to inner demons.
I've seen this fruit on planet Suzaku before
but I never thought it existed in the Demon Spirit Land.
You just won't leave me alone !
The fiend has finally summoned me !
If I perform today,
I'm sure he'll forgive me for my betrayal.
Hey ! Hey ! Hey !
Who dares to harm my Master ?!
Master,
save me !
Demonic Finger !
Is this thing
destroyed ?
Something's wrong...
The armor is the source of the demonic aura !
You...
are mine !
Master, be careful !
Life and Death Reincarnation Cycle !
This sound disturbs my soul,
it's nauseating.
With my mind blurred,
I'm just meat
on his plate.
You are mine.
I must...
stay conscious...
Since I can't fight fair...
then...
I'll use my killing intent !
Kill !
Kill !!
Kill !!!
You...
Reincarnation cycle...
Annihilation !
He dares to use killing intent against me !?
Madman !
This one has succumbed to inner demons.
Capturing him would cost more
than the origin energy I'll gain.
It wouldn't benefit me
to capture him now.
Enough.
I accumulated energy for tens of thousands of years,
I can't lose it all now.
Are you fleeing now ?
Found you...
M...Master...
shouldn't we heal our wounds first ?
What ?
N...N...Nothing !
What I meant was...
we need to strike now while he's off-guard !
We're doomed...
The fiend of the Sea of Devils is back.
No, wait...
he's even more terrifying than before.
Those who disturb my Ascendant breakthrough
must die !
A mere Early stage Ascendant
dares to provoke me !?
Ten Thousand Demons Heart Devouring !
Central Plains\NFire Demon Country
Is that all you've got ?
A single drop of this wine knocked you out for a year
but you just swallowed 4 drops !
You're crazy !
Come at me !
Exhilarating !
Make it more exhilarating !
His body is dead,
his Origin Soul is collapsing.
Yet, fueled by the Celestial Ascension Fruits and celestial spiritual energy,
he is growing even more insane.
At this speed...
Indeed,
we're already in the Central Plains.
But since you're acting so conspicuously,
the Fire Demon Country is bound to notice.
You're courting death.
Zi Shu\NDa Lou Sword Sect disciple\NPeak Late stage Soul Transformation
An Ascendant cultivator ?
And a severely injured one at that...
This is a heaven-sent opportunity !
If I devour his Ascendant Origin Soul,
it will benefit my Sword Spirit !
All troops, stand by.
Stay here.
Such a fresh
killing intent.
You are gravely injured,
stop clinging to life !
Thanks for the medicine.
The Commander
is dead !
Kill him !
Avenge the Commander !
Kill !
Death Finger...
Imperial Palace\NFire Demon Country
Reporting to His Majesty,
Zi Shu's army
has been annihilated.
Demon Emperor\NFire Demon Country
He slaughtered 30 000 of my soldiers ?
I will
carve out his heart and bones !
Issue the order,
summon 100 000 troops.
I'll use this madman's blood
to color my land !
Understood !
What an intense killing intent...
Tianyi City\NFire Demon Country
You killed my Commander
Xuan Qi\NFire Demon Country Commander-in-chief\NRank 300 000 Demonic Energy\N(Early stage Ascendant)
and slaughtered my soldiers.
But now I will
execute you right away
by imperial decree !
Activate...
the Abyssal Demon Inferno Formation !
Kill !
Death...
Finger !
A mere Early stage Ascendant
dares to run rampant in my Fire Demon Country !?
The Abyssal Demon Inferno Formation
combines the strength of 100 000 soldiers
by using an Ascendant as the formation core.
Let alone you,
even a Late stage Ascendant
wouldn't escape it alive.
In a desperate situation
I swallowed these blood-red fruits.
The Celestial Wine scorches
my throat and soul.
All troops, hear my order !
By the Emperor's decree,
we will kill this man !
Pain severed
the locks on my nerves.
Don't let him escape !
A madman's smile
appears in the corner of my mouth.
Kill ! Kill ! Kill !
My killing move falls like the rain. Pun intented
as I laugh maniacally.
Let my sword slice through bones and flesh.
Savoring this
near-death epiphany.
Adrenaline
rushes through my veins.
As far as I can see,
everybody is my prey.
The lucidity of being possessed
is the deepest curse.
Killing intent
overflows and cannot be contained.
This killing intent...
is truly intoxicating.
Break through this path to the underworld.
With the reincarnation cycle as your prison,
you are condemned to eternal damnation.
Impossible...
This city will serve as your tomb.
Break through this path to the underworld.
With the reincarnation cycle as your prison,
you are condemned to eternal damnation.
This city will serve as your tomb.
He intends to break the formation !
Underworld Finger...
Fall !
This...
this isn't possible !
He just reached Ascendant,
Kill through your path of destiny
how could he have his own Dao ?
Through slaughter I shall prove my Dao,
The Dao of the Underworld...
let the heavens and the earth bow down to me,
a king crowned in madness.
By using the Celestial Ascension Fruits, the Celestial Wine,
and the killing intent of this huge army to temper me,
Break through this path to the underworld.
I've actually begun to grasp what the second step is:
With the reincarnation cycle as your prison,
you are condemned to eternal damnation.
materializing the heart's desires into reality.
This city will serve as your tomb.
Interesting...
From now on,
I, Wang Lin, will cultivate neither the heavens nor the earth,
neither celestials nor gods,
I cultivate only my own Dao.
Whoever wishes to kill me
shall be trapped in my Underworld River,
my own reincarnation cycle
free from the heavens and the earth !
I am the underworld.
I am the reincarnation cycle.
I am the end.
With only an Early stage Ascendant cultivation,
he has opened up his own underworld river...
Wang Lin...
you truly amaze me.
Ming Yuan !
Ming Yuan\NRank 500 000 Demonic Energy\N(Late stage Ascendant)
Master, what's your order ?
Get ready to welcome our guest.
In the donghua the Celestial Ascension Fruits were renamed to the Demonic Possession Fruits. I disagree with that terminology. The state Wang Lin ends up in after consuming the fruit is due to his inner killing intent plus the fact that he overused the Demonic Finger before Ascendant and also because he cultivated the Celestial Slaughter Art. For other people the fruits will have other effects and this has implications later in the story. We'll see how they adapt it now...\NAlso, it was shown but not explained, the Death Finger can absorb energy.\N\NThese fruits are only the size of a baby’s fist, and they are completely purple and give off a strange fragrance. If a person were to eat one, they would become excited and feel extreme pleasures. This is why this fruit is called Celestial Ascension Fruit.\N\NIf a mortal were to eat one, they would become addicted, but it wouldn’t affect a cultivator much. However, there are cultivators who enjoy eating the fruit and losing themselves in that intoxicating feeling.\N\NIn the mortal world, only the rich and powerful can get Celestial Ascension Fruits from cultivators after paying a heavy price. Then they can immerse themselves in the intoxicating feeling like they have become celestials themselves.
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
Nascent Soul
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
Soul Transformation
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
Ascendant
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.